Music
Hello everyone, I'm Yuka Murayama and Emi Ichihara from Nearly Call Joy!
We're Yuka Murayama and Emi Ichihara of Nearly Call Joy.
Today, we had the pleasure of renting out the Plaza before it opened!
Thank you very much!
It's a little bit strange...
I know.
It's still quiet.
This time, we're going to have a 30-minute cosmetics shopping spree at the Plaza!
Yay!
Bakubai!
Bakubyaku (explosive shopping)
That's amazing!
It's my first time, right? It's my first time. I'm going to have a lot of fun. I'll see you later.
Where are you going? Where are we going? Come on, let's go. You use Excel. Which one do you use? Which one do you use? The eyeshadow.
This one.
We're about to run out of number 10.
I'm going to buy this one, the one I always use.
Aiming for something I'm interested in, I had a hair/makeup artist apply a lipstick and I thought it was a cute color, so if I can find that lipstick, I'd like to buy it.
I'd like to buy some of the famous Momo of Swisse's Momo, I don't have it, I don't have it, I don't have it.
I don't have it... I don't have it... I don't have it... I don't have it... I don't know, it's cute.
The most popular is the one that is used to make the eye bags.
I think I saw a tanning product over there... or maybe it was over there... in the summer section...
Wow, so cute! Lilimu, so cute!
Ayumi is using a grid, isn't she?
Ayumi's using grid.
She always uses this one... when she's at a concert or something.
Seek is cute. It's so cute! It's so cute! It's really good. What's this? What's this? It's really good. What's this?
It's a primer for dry skin.
It's good for dry skin, but it's too sticky for oily skin.
I've been wanting this gloss for a long time.
I'm so happy. - No. 05. Tibmorb.
Oh, good, good. You want to buy it?
I heard it's great for blues.
I think a lot of Laka members use this lipstick.
I use them too. The colors are pretty. They're pretty.
I usually use 106?
Lips are so exciting. What kind do you like? Blue Berkers are so hard to find. I can't decide for myself.
I like darker colors, but since it's summer, I'd like to try something a little brighter.
Blue is also pink, which is definitely a color I don't have. I've never tried this color before.
I've never tried this color.
Summer of 2024!
I'd like to buy Laka 110 then.
Great! Get it!
Oh, no.
Only 20 minutes left.
It's not in yet.
I guess I'm just in the mood to buy.
Oh, he's back.
Can I talk to you for a second?
I always use Maybelline.
I've always used Maybelline Liquid Fun.
Number 103.
Always?
It's getting a little normal.
I think I need to apply more than I do in the winter.
I know it's easy to fall apart in the summer.
I'd like to get it.
I'll put it in.
Yay!
I love it! I love it!
I heard that one of our fans at dinner told me that she uses Meibilin, and I told her that she already uses Meibilin, and she bought it.
I told him that I already use Maybilin, and he bought it.
I'm going to buy some more Libby New... I'm going to buy some more Libby New too.
I like Ayumi's tear macros.
I'd like to match the same one a little bit... I'm so glad I got the 03-03-03 glitter!
I'd like to use it at the show.
It's really cute, not too flashy.
It's really pretty, not too flashy, and it's not too bright when it hits the light.
It makes my eyes sparkle.
It's beautiful. I'm so happy.
I'm so happy. Thank you.
Can I take a look at your sunscreen products? Can we go to the summer section? I think you should go to the summer section. Let's go.
Summer. Lots of summer.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
I use a lot at one time. Which one has the most amount?
No foundation, no UV, no foundation, no foundation?
A little purple.
A little purple, tone-up kind of thing. Oh, wow! It tones up! Is this good for the face? It says "face." Smells good! Smells great!
It smells so good. But it's also good for your body.
I'm curious. It's stylish, stylish, stylish. Is it for the body? It can be used for face and body.
I'm gonna get it. I'm getting it! You want to take a look? Yes, let's.
What is this? Keep Mist? I've never seen that before! I'm curious!
Maybe I'll get some? Yay!
That's awesome! What about the lotion type? This way?
You want me to put it over here or not?
I'm curious.
Glutathione C.
You mean like a whitening lotion?
It's like a pack.
It's amazing.
It's light.
People who think they got sunburned today can put it on at night
It's also good to revive the skin.
There's something about this one, too.
What is this?
Lotion.
It's a lotion.
It's a lotion with glutathione and vitamins.
Here you go.
Instead of putting on a pack, just put on a lotion and let it soak in.
I'm going to take in a lot of it.
I think it's better for me to take in a lot of vitamins.
I'd like to get this one.
I'd like to get this one, too.
Packs.
Is there? I don't know.
I don't know.
I'm using this pack.
It's from this series.
It helps with acne and red pimples.
It's great.
It's a vitamin pack.
You're interested in it, right?
It's summer, after all.
It's a bit of a first for me, but...
I'm going to go with this vitamin bag.
Yay!
Oh, no! Ten minutes left!
Oh, no!
I think I might have found a parasol on the ground.
Isn't this a parasol?
A parasol looks good on you, Ayumi.
Isn't it convenient to carry?
Put it in your bag.
It's cute.
It's nice and convenient to carry, and you can use it rain or shine.
I'm looking at it.
It's a little bit addictive.
It's got 100% UV protection. Which color do you like?
If you're using black, I'll go with white.
I think I'll go with white. Yay! I got it!
I like it.
Yay!
You have five more, don't you?
What do you want?
You want some? Yeah, let's see.
Oh, my God. So many eyeshadows.
Wow! So many!
So cute.
I might need some eyeshadows.
These are so cute.
What? I worked so hard.
It's so pretty.
Isn't this one really pretty?
She's so pretty.
There's another one above.
This eyeshadow.
It's also very Bleu-Bleu.
So cute!
Cute.
This one looks good, too.
It's pretty natural. It's shiny and cute. I'm kind of curious about this one.
Can I get one of those? It's gonna be the same one, but it's gonna be matching.
Nice. It's a lovely Boulevardose. You're Clio, right, Clio?
You want me to get it? Oh, I only have one, so no. No way. What am I going to do? No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Are you kidding me? You sure? Yeah, it's okay.
What is this? Power? Is this a cushion foundation?
Do you use it? I use a cushion foundation. Do you recommend it?
It's easy. I think I use a cushion foundation when I want to fix something.
I've never used a cushion foundation. Really? You should try it.
Which one do you recommend? I don't know.
This one? I've used this one. It's a different color.
But I think this is the most recent one.
Oh, really? This one?
Yeah, it's new.
When I knew you, this was all you had.
Now it's new.
Well, can I try it?
That's good, that's good, that's good.
This is a cushion foundation. I'll try it.
Aimin'.
Get it!
That's good.
Okay, good.
One minute left.
Oh, shit. One minute left.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm not one of those "no regrets" kind of guys... not the "oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
I've been wanting to try something new, and this tray looks really good.
I'm going to try a new one...
Citrus.
I'm going to try this one.
It's good, it's good, it's good, it moisturizes the skin.
I'll get this one. - Yeah, get it!
Ayumi?
I'm really interested in And Honey around here.
I like it. What kind do you like?
The silky kind? Moist?
I'm thinking moist. I don't know about moist.
This one looks thick, so I'll get it for my dry hair.
I'm gonna let it soak in.
That's good. That's good.
It's good, right?
It's good, right? I'm so happy because I really wanted a hair oil. I'm so happy.
I'm so happy that I was able to buy so many products that I wanted. I'm happy that I was able to get some products that I'm interested in.
Let's go to the cash register.
Is this it? Is the cash register here?
I just spent 30,000 yen!
That's a lot of money! You just made a big purchase!
33,508 yen!
I am very satisfied!
Thank you so much for your wonderful project!
I am too happy!
Yes, so I bought a lot!
Did I buy a lot?
So many! Compared to Yuuka, I bought a little too much.
I bought a little too much!
I bought a lot of different kinds of packs, oils, eye shadows, suntan lotion, and so on.
I bought all kinds of packs, oils, eye shadows, and even sunscreen!
If you enjoyed this video, please give it a high rating, subscribe to the channel, and leave a comment!
That's all for now, this is Nyarikoruru JOY!